welcome to Mythbusters why the strange
欢迎来到神话破坏者，为什么奇怪
title of the session heavyweight versus
重量级的会议标题vs
lightweight because I get exactly the
轻巧的，因为我得到了
questions all over the time actually
实际上一直在提问
yesterday someone on Twitter said
昨天有人在推特上说
someone in the session meant Java is too
会议中有人表示Java也是如此
heavy weight and what it means actually
沉重的重量，这实际上意味着什么
I don't know ask the speaker I have no
我不知道问演讲者我没有
idea what it means and in projects I can
知道这意味着什么，在项目中我可以
tell you stories over and over again in
一遍又一遍地告诉你故事
one project they wanted to have
他们想要的一个项目
micro-services as a huge shop they had
微服务作为他们拥有的庞大商店
several hundred Java EE applications so
数百个Java EE应用程序
I mean real Java applications which
我的意思是真正的Java应用程序
means application server and then say
表示应用程序服务器，然后说
all for micro-services it won't work
全部用于微服务，将无法正常工作
anymore and the idea was to use just
不再是这个想法了
jetty and I was asked how to do this I
码头，我被问到如何做到这一点
look at this is where okay this was a
看这是好地方
lifetime for me job because then you
一生为我工作，因为那时你
know we have to make a jetty to work
知道我们必须跳码头才能工作
like an application server with the
就像带有
dependency injection and everything else
依赖注入和其他一切
and the question is what we will gain do
问题是我们将获得的成就
you really believe that if I will you
你真的相信，如果我愿意你
know patch jetty for you that it will
为您了解斑驳码头
behave like a fake application server at
表现得像假冒的应用程序服务器
the end of the day I'm going to be
一天的结束，我将成为
smarter than you know the whole white
比你知道的还要聪明
fly or PI R or Thome team and mice
飞行或PI R或Thome小组和老鼠
application server is going to be
应用服务器将是
smaller and they say actually all right
较小，他们说实际上没事
and what happened was in this particular
发生了什么事
case they ditched after the presentation
他们在演讲后抛弃的情况
jetty and they went with payara fool in
码头，他们和帕亚拉傻瓜一起去了
this case in production in other
这种情况在其他生产中
projects white flight fool or Tomy plus
项目白班傻瓜或托米加
what I never used is you see why now
我没用过的是你现在明白为什么
after the discourse anything was web
话语之后，一切都是网络
profile because there was no measurable
个人资料，因为没有可衡量的
difference in my project if I cannot
如果我做不到，我的项目就会有所不同
measure I don't like such optimization
措施我不喜欢这样的优化
so I always use the full application
所以我总是使用完整的应用程序
server and even I think even if it has
服务器，甚至我认为，即使有
to run on the Raspberry Pi or doesn't
在Raspberry Pi上运行还是不运行
make any difference so it makes a huge
有所作为，所以它带来了巨大的变化
difference for the for the application
应用的区别
server vendors because if they have to
服务器供应商，因为如果他们必须
provide the full platform they have a
提供他们拥有的完整平台
lot work to do they have to implement
他们要做很多工作
the old stuff who no one cares about
没人关心的旧东西
what I am down the window okay and the
我在窗下好吗，
user of the application service and for
应用程序服务的用户
me I forgot to mention of course you can
我我忘了提当然可以
ask me questions whenever like so the
在任何时候问我问题
first question
第一个问题
yes we will look at this during this
是的，我们将在此期间看一下
session I have I will launch a swarm and
会议上，我将发动一群
PR a swarm and if you have other swarms
PR一群，如果还有其他一群
we can launch whatever is accessible
我们可以启动任何可访问的
right and measure this so yeah and what
正确并测量这一点，是的，还有什么
I do usually it is very dangerous to be
我通常这样做很危险
involved in such discussions because if
参与这样的讨论，因为如果
you start to argue with what is
你开始争论什么是
heavyweight and lightweight this is
重量轻巧的这是
never-ending meeting I mean there will
无休止的会议，我的意思是
be no winner so what do you do we stop
没有胜利者，那么我们该怎么办
the meeting right away go home provide a
会议马上回家
proof of concept create read update
概念验证创建读取更新
delete with the performance test measure
用性能测试手段删除
the result and say look these are the
结果，说看这些是
numbers now you can decide you know is
数字，现在您可以决定知道
it worth to save I don't know five makes
值得保存，我不知道五个品牌
twenty makes five hundred Meg's to geek
二十使五百梅格成为极客
or whatever and if someone says okay if
或其他什么，如果有人说，如果
we do this we save five thousand dollars
我们这样做可以节省五千美元
or twenty thousand dollars then it is no
或两万美元，那不是
or yes but there's no more in my
还是可以，但是我的内no
decision the sad story is if you do this
决定悲伤的故事是，如果你这样做
you will always stick with application
您将始终坚持申请
service so if you would like it to your
服务，所以如果您愿意
life more exciting in some more
生活更加精彩
experiments don't do this what I do yeah
实验不做我该做的
I have a web blog and in workshops and
我有一个网络博客，并在研讨会中
this is properly interesting so just
这很有趣，所以
like question and answer and then during
喜欢问题和答案，然后在
the last its first Monday of the month
最后一个月的第一个星期一
at 6 p.m. CET I forgot what is actually
欧洲中部时间下午6点，我忘记了实际上是什么
hear us minus 9 hours I think and and I
听到我们减去9个小时，我想，我
have no time to answer questions via
没有时间通过​​回答问题
email so I do this live streaming and
电子邮件，所以我可以进行直播
someone asked me they use undertow this
有人问我他们用这种方式
is like the HTTP server from whitefly
就像来自whitefly的HTTP服务器
and they would like to have just the
他们只想拥有
undertow in jax-rs and they are pretty
在jax-rs中露面，他们很漂亮
far but it depends a dependency
远，但这取决于依赖性
injection does not work so I wanted
注射无效，所以我想
answered no time what what interests me
没时间回答我有什么兴趣
how much time they spend to optimize
他们花了多少时间进行优化
this and if they are ready and it will
这，如果他们准备好了，它将
work which problem do they have first
他们首先遇到什么问题
this will be unique combination of
这将是
technologies just for the project they
仅用于项目的技术
created their own application server and
创建了自己的应用程序服务器，
what we were already interesting to see
我们已经很有趣的看到了什么
whether this application server is
该应用服务器是否为
faster smaller or more lightweight
更快或更小或更轻
whatever it means than the actual white
比实际的白色意味着什么
line so I asked them why do not start
行，所以我问他们为什么不开始
with white fly and then delete whatever
白飞，然后删除任何内容
you don't like why you create your own
你不喜欢为什么创建自己的
no no answer because properly it was
不，没有答案，因为正确
easy to do this okay so um so I start
容易做到这一点好吧，所以我开始
always with definitions because someone
总是带有定义，因为有人
heavyweight and lightweight this is
重量轻巧的这是
dictionary I just fired up a pair
我刚开了一对字典
screenshot and what it means heavyweight
屏幕截图及其重量级
is okay boxing does not apply apply to
没关系，拳击不适用于
application servers above average weight
超过平均重量的应用服务器
this could be ands it the cool story is
这可能是最有趣的故事
the adjective this serious important or
形容词这个非常重要的
influential this would be heavy weight
有影响力的这将是沉重的
there so okay if yes then Java is
那里很好，如果可以，那么Java是
extremely heavy weight okay so otherwise
非常重，好吧，否则
light weight means sometimes is is you
轻巧意味着有时候是你
know this is in the amateur boxing scale
知道这是业余拳击秤
it ranges from 57 to 60 kilogram so but
它的重量从57到60公斤不等
the adjective means lacking seriousness
形容词手段缺乏严肃性
depth or influence is entertaining it
深度或影响力使之有趣
rather lightweight this is what I see
相当轻巧，这就是我所看到的
all these solutions I saw which were
我看到的所有这些解决方案是
lightweight
轻巧的
they were entertaining but rather
他们很有趣，但是
lightweight it means meaningless okay so
轻巧意味着没有意义，所以
um if you come to projects and say to is
嗯，如果你来参加项目并说是
too heavy weight and I am in the project
太重了，我在项目中
I will ask you what startup time REM
我会问你几点启动时间
download size CPU overhead what do you
下载大小CPU开销你是什么
mean or is this just marketing sorry
的意思是或者这仅仅是行销对不起
so okay this was the last light this is
好吧，这是最后一盏灯
just some workshops and this is the last
只是一些工作坊，这是最后一个
line thank you so the question is what I
行谢谢你，所以问题是我
would like to do is to start some
想做的就是开始一些
application service like something for
应用服务就像
you and measure this and the question is
你，并衡量这一点，问题是
we get some numbers out so application
我们得到一些数字，所以应用
servers full I just will use full and I
服务器已满，我将使用已满，我
always use the micros because you asked
总是使用micros，因为你问
so the question is to what we should
所以问题是我们应该怎么做
compare the numbers I mean if this
比较我的意思是，如果这
what's coming out is heavyweight we have
出来的是重量级的
to have a comparison to something right
比较正确的东西
which is lightweight what would it be
这是轻量级的
huh yeah it will use works as well so
嗯，它也会使用工程，所以
what's there is already in but what else
已经有什么，还有什么
yeah and Tomcat is too boring what I
是的，Tomcat太无聊了
will do is the create an ultimate micro
要做的就是创造最终的微
service what yeah what WebLogic I I have
服务什么，WebLogic II拥有什么
it but I did not the recent version but
它，但我没有最新版本，但是
I measured in the past so I will tell
我曾经测量过，所以我会告诉
the numbers I could try to launch it but
我可以尝试启动它的数字，但是
didn't launch it for long time WebLogic
长时间没有启动它WebLogic
drop wizard yeah what I will do even
下降向导是的，我什至会做什么
worse I will provide something white
更糟糕的是我会提供白色
white less yeah
白少耶
white less or lightweight and absolutely
白色少或重量轻，绝对
meaningless so what I would like to do
没有意义，所以我想做什么
is to create the ultimate
是创造最终
micro-service actual an eunuch colonel
微服务实际的一个太监上校
and I will start with a jar I mean this
我将以一个罐子开始
ultimate thing would be Java C project
最终的事情将是Java C项目
and call it white main oh okay I hope
并称它为白色主哦，我希望
this was the right one
这是正确的
and this is nothing it's just just a
这没什么，只是一个
pump and what I would like to do is I
泵，我想做的是
would like to create a Java class and
想要创建一个Java类，并
call it calm yeah thanks Nana
冷静点吧，谢谢娜娜
and then one main method public public
然后是一种主要的方法public public
static void main and serversocket right
静态void main和serverocket权利
what let's say 1990 hopefully is not
假设1990年不是
used new and destroy some exceptions the
使用新的并销毁一些异常
variable socket and then Zorka dot
可变插座，然后是Zorka点
accept what I get back is the socket and
接受我得到的是插座和
at least dual block so we can measure
至少是双重块，所以我们可以测量
how much whim it will receive and I
它会收到多少异想天开，我
would say regardless what you are doing
会说不管你在做什么
this is the absolute lightweightness
这是绝对的轻量化
right there there will be no other drop
那里不会有其他下落
with our Tomcats nanos or whatever which
用我们的Tomcats nanos或其他任何东西
are smaller than this so this is our
小于这个，所以这是我们的
reference
参考
there's the smallest possible server
最小的服务器
with single threaded like note but the
单线像笔记，但
little server agreed so I think this is
小服务器同意，所以我认为这是
this is reasonable
这是合理的
this is socket sorry this is it's called
这是套接字，抱歉，这叫做
ass and ass get out get out put stream I
屁股和屁股滚滚滚滚滚滚而来
guess and then right
猜对然后对
white less get bytes I think it should
白色少获取字节我认为应该
work so I would just build ant or just
工作，所以我会建立蚂蚁或只是
go to the command line this is in junk
转到命令行，这是垃圾
folder no no maven package then we
文件夹没有没有Maven包，那么我们
should get T on target and I say Java
应该让T达到目标，我说Java
minus CP this is not executable target
减去CP，这不是可执行目标
and what was it this was this and calm
这是什么，这是平静的
air hex and I think Nano right so it
空气六角，我认为纳米是正确的
once cool right
曾经很酷的权利
this is the future nano service so if
这是未来的纳米服务，所以如果
you would like to be no famous
你想不出名
conference speaker no dependencies throw
会议发言人没有依赖性
away everything else go to your drop
离开一切都落在你身上
wizard guys and say your application
向导们说你的申请
server are to heavyweight use this so
服务器要重量级使用此
then J visual VM launch it what do you
然后J visual VM启动它，你做什么
expect
期望
so it uses size 25
所以它使用尺寸25
250 max is this total consumption and
总消耗量最大为250，
right now it uses 60 16 megabyte of RAM
现在它使用60 16 MB的RAM
so what it means regardless what we are
所以不管我们是什么意思
doing it would be never better than this
这样做永远不会比这更好
everyone agrees
大家都同意
so it's JD k-19 I could do some streaks
所以是JD k-19我可以做一些条纹
with the module loaders the question is
与模块装载机的问题是
if I have such problems either the
如果我有这样的问题
application server is supposed to run on
应用服务器应该在
Apple watch right or we have serious
苹果手表正确，否则我们会认真对待
budget problems because I know how about
预算问题，因为我知道
us but in Germany I can buy 64 gigabyte
我们，但在德国，我可以购买64 GB
of ECC Ram for server for about 400
服务器的ECC Ram数量约为400
euros so if I run the performance a
欧元，所以如果我运行性能
garbage collector you see it is 7 Meg
垃圾收集器，您看到它是7兆欧
but I will have to run it frequently
但我必须经常运行
because there is no pressure so it will
因为没有压力所以它将
never optimize to this ok everyone
永远不要为此优化所有人
agreed good experiment right and this
同意好的实验权，这
should actually work so if I go here and
应该实际工作，所以如果我去这里，
say Curl Curl let's see what localhost
说Curl Curl让我们看看localhost是什么
1980 would cool right you see how
1980年会很酷，你看如何
lightweight java is try this with note
轻量级的Java是带注释的尝试
more code no and with Java SE verts out
更多代码否，并且使用Java SE淘汰了
of the box now application server so the
的盒子现在的应用服务器，所以
easiest to me is to start white phial
对我来说最容易的是启动白色玻璃瓶
payara
帕亚拉
because i have them and amuse them in
因为我有它们并在其中逗乐
the projects so this is white flight n-1
项目，所以这是白色的航班n-1
full is the current one there is 11
满是当前的一个，有11个
something but this is the full payara
东西，但这是全薪
you can download a payara white flight
您可以下载payara白色航班
and if you go to white fly so we can
如果你去白蝇，那么我们可以
check for instance download right now
立即检查实例下载
and what I use all applications of a
以及我使用的所有应用程序
distribution I use the full one the
分配我用完整的
biggest largest of course ten one full
最大最大当然十一个全
web and distribution and there are 134
网络和发行，有134
megabyte download size so this is the
兆字节下载大小，所以这是
largest available white light the others
最大可用白光
are around 150 as well so it means if
也都在150左右
you find a technology it will be always
您发现一项技术将永远
hopefully smaller than this the question
希望比这个小
is do we have problem with that this is
是我们有问题吗
like you know 5 iPhone pictures I would
就像你知道5张iPhone图片一样
say
说
okay everything else what the download
好的，其他所有下载
is usually larger than this some iPhone
通常比某些iPhone大
apps are larger than 150 EPS so the
应用大于150 EPS，因此
question is what's the problem and I
问题是什么问题，我
build them frequently in docker image
经常在Docker映像中构建它们
and even the download size is not a
甚至下载大小也不是
problem but therefore I use the largest
问题，但因此我使用最大的
one if you look here for instance
例如，如果你看这里
servlet only is 28
servlet只有28
just servlets but I never saw just a
只是servlet，但我从未见过
servlet in production in my projects for
我项目中生产中的servlet
me sometimes we build load balancers
我有时我们会建立负载平衡器
just with servlets but I mean usually
仅使用servlet，但我的意思通常是
you would need something else so it
您还需要其他东西
means the reference here would be 28 mix
意味着这里的参考是28混合
right so it's the smallest possible
对，所以它是最小的
white light okay so now I start that and
白光好，所以现在我开始
this is not there's a little bit
这没有一点
cheating but they are cheating in in in
作弊，但他们在欺骗
my disadvantage because this white fly
我的缺点是因为这只白蝇
is already I has this highest monitoring
我已经有这个最高的监控了
setup so there's the most overhead so
设置，所以有最大的开销，所以
we're measuring here is the DD large as
我们在这里测量的DD是
possible all that so let's go here to
可能所有的一切，让我们去这里
the visual and we see here JBoss full
视觉，我们在这里看到JBoss完整
click to monitor and we see 87 Meg used
单击以监视，我们看到使用了87 Meg
without any changes perform GC we see it
无需任何更改即可执行GC我们看到了
goes down to 40 Meg what we had in Java
下降到40 Meg我们在Java中所拥有的
were five Meg's right or six seven so
是五个梅格的权利或六个七的权利
what it means the very good so we have
这意味着什么很好，所以我们有
to be precise here otherwise you know I
确切地说，否则你知道我
get lots of trouble so so we have seven
遇到很多麻烦所以我们有七个
max with Java SE the full white fly in
Java SE的最大提升
idle takes that just goes up because out
空闲时间会增加，因为
of the box it comes with minus X and mix
附带X的盒子
setting so it is less pressure on the
设置，这样可以减轻压力
JVM to college the garbage so what do I
JVM让垃圾变成垃圾，那我该怎么办
have to do is to make it comparable
要做的就是使其具有可比性
remove all the settings then would be
删除所有设置，然后将
less but we see if I perform the garbage
少点，但我们看看我是否执行垃圾
collection then this is around 35 Meg so
收集，然后大约是35兆，所以
it means we can save 30 megabyte of RAM
这意味着我们可以节省30 MB的RAM
per microservice in production now in my
现在我的生产中每个微服务
project we have at most 20 micro
项目我们最多有20个
services it will means 20 teams which
服务将意味着20个团队
are independent it means in the full
是独立的，这意味着完全
setup in my client we could save 600 mix
在我的客户中设置可以节省600个混音
of RAM
的RAM
now imagine me and say forget your
现在想像我，说忘记你的
application service we should be more
应用服务我们应该更多
lightweight if we do this and it's
轻量的，如果我们这样做，它是
a few days we will we will save one time
几天，我们将节省一次
probably 600 mix over m and the main
大约600混合在米和主要
client will ask is the enterprise
客户会问是企业
companies or money rules right there are
公司或金钱规则就在那里
not like Tequesta say okay how much is
不像Tequesta说好的，多少钱
it like approximately 5 cents and they
大概5美分，他们
say ok a completely strange right you
说好吧，你完全陌生
can say what's about clouds so I did
可以说云到底是什么，所以我做了
some payara and white fur and Amazon
一些payara和白色的皮毛和亚马逊
accs and I forgot to do to disable the
accs，我忘了禁用它
cloud with ELB and it cost me $16 per
云与ELB，每张成本为16美元
month to white flies in an ill be
一个月到白色苍蝇病
running all the time so the question is
一直运行，所以问题是
there a larger company and you could
有一个更大的公司，你可以
save 50% to $8 a month what's the
每月节省50％至$ 8
difference I mean is it significant ok
差异，我的意思是，这很重要吗
so now we have what white light done
所以现在我们做了白光
who said WebSphere okay try WebSphere so
谁说WebSphere可以，请尝试使用WebSphere这样
I'm just please remind me to stop the
我只是请提醒我停止
service so WebSphere is in different
服务，因此WebSphere与众不同
folder
夹
I installed web seon service so this is
我安装了Web seon服务，所以这是
the last one and so this is the start
最后一个，所以这是开始
this is not the WebSphere kernel what I
这不是WebSphere内核
did already
已经
I I said it this way that it uses the
II这样说，它使用
Java 7 web profile plus dependencies and
Java 7 Web配置文件以及相关性和
this is the Webster you can you can get
这是您可以获得的韦伯斯特
with the web c license this is the newer
使用Web c许可证，这是较新的
one so let's go here in the and we see
一个，让我们在这里去，我们看到
here
这里
comm i BN website kernel boot this is
comm i BN网站内核启动这是
deep protest so i switch here monitor
强烈抗议，所以我在这里切换显示器
and we see it is 90 megabyte of RAM
我们看到它是90 MB的RAM
perform GC goes down to 40 so what it
执行GC下降到40
means
手段
Webster is you could a safe with white
韦伯斯特是你可以放心使用白色
fly to Mexico
飞到墨西哥
compare compared to WebSphere deployment
与WebSphere部署相比
in all application service a small war
在所有应用服务中的一场小战
complies usually about in one second
通常一秒钟左右
this is what it takes
这就是需要的
of course the more crazy the application
当然，应用程序越疯狂
gets you
让你
that takes what the cool story is why I
这就是为什么我很酷的故事
like actually Java E is because to the
就像实际上的Java E是因为
wars are always small because there is
战争总是很小，因为
nothing in there everything is on the
那里什么都没有
application server the diplomas are
应用服务器的文凭
always crazy fast actually in one
总是总是快疯了
project I said use Java e and then
我说的项目使用Java e然后
complained is not as fast as you said it
抱怨不如你说的那么快
takes five seconds and what we noticed
需要五秒钟，我们注意到了
they had a virus until a virus scanner
他们感染了病毒直到病毒扫描仪
and it scanned everything before
它扫描了之前的所有内容
something could deploy it I mean this
有些东西可以部署它，我的意思是
was a different story but so if you are
是一个不同的故事，但是如果你是
complaining about the deployment
抱怨部署
performance check really or other make
确实进行性能检查或其他
the virus scanners so they scan
病毒扫描程序，以便他们扫描
everything so this was WebSphere a
一切，所以这是WebSphere a
Liberty profile and in I forgot actually
自由简介，我实际上忘记了
I think this one's on ninety eighty
我认为这是九十八岁
WebSphere this is a localhost ninety
WebSphere这是 localhost 90
eighty I guess yeah and with full Java
八十岁，我想是的，并且拥有完整的Java
seven support and module are you can you
七个支持和模块就可以了
have full command line so what I can do
有完整的命令行，所以我能做什么
is serve a list there are all these
服务清单上有所有这些
servers I can dump them archive here I
我可以将其存档的服务器转储到这里
you can create service and close them on
您可以创建服务并关闭它们
the fly so this is what's the Liberty
苍蝇，所以这就是自由
profile so I would I would do spy era
配置文件，所以我会做间谍时代
and by the way WebLogic would start with
顺便说一下，WebLogic将以
100 Meg and this is the largest one and
100兆欧，这是最大的一个
the overhead would be a perfect I think
我认为开销是完美的
I recorded a screencast about web
我录制了有关网络的截屏视频
project as well and it was like 90 Meg's
以及90兆的麦格
or something like this so it was the
或类似的东西，所以这是
largest but it's still not a problem so
最大，但这仍然不是问题，所以
it's not like it took 500 Meg's it was
好像不是花了500兆欧
like twice as large I think like a white
大概是白色的两倍
files like ATM X or something like this
像ATM X之类的文件
so you can always argue no webs web
所以你总是可以说没有网
logic is heavy weight because it's twice
逻辑很重，因为它是两倍
as large I was white flight like what it
像我一样大
means the numbers ATM exams okay what
意思是数字ATM考试好吗
problem do we have whose item X and by
问题是我们有谁的项目X和
the way which is always a good thing to
永远是一件好事的方式
compare this with Chrome and my test
将此与Chrome和我的测试进行比较
window takes now 70 Meg's of RAM so what
窗口现在需要70 Meg的RAM，所以
it means if you are really really about
这意味着如果你真的是真的
lightweightness never open a browser
轻量级永不打开浏览器
okay so so we have white fly we have the
好吧，所以我们有白蝇，我们有
Liberty if you like payara
自由，如果你喜欢payara
para would be similar so we should do
段落将类似，所以我们应该做
this right now to be complete so
现在要完成，所以
server stop and it stops the default
服务器停止并停止默认
server and what do you have to do to
服务器，您需要做什么
configure this so if you go here to user
进行配置，以便您访问用户
what I did
我做了什么
servers default server can't server.xml
服务器默认服务器不能server.xml
sorry so this is the full configuration
抱歉，这是完整配置
this is the I had to tell website use
这是我不得不告诉网站的使用
web profile 7 oh there is no full
网站资料7哦，没有完整的
profile there is something like web
个人资料中有类似网络的内容
profile plus dependencies but it does
配置文件加上依赖关系，但它确实
matter this eg B's and CDI everything is
不管这个，例如B和CDI都是
included already ok payara this is not
包括已经可以了，这不是
the most recent one because I use this
最近的一个因为我用这个
in production and so start that and I
在生产中，所以开始那个，我
wouldn't like to start the glass 55
不想启动玻璃55
because it's like payara without patches
因为就像没有补丁的payara
right so so it starts right now
对，所以现在就开始
and take a look at this and you see it
看看这个，你看到了
comes this is already no more comparable
来了，这已经不再具有可比性
because it comes with - mix 512 megabyte
因为它附带-混合512 MB
of RAM but if we go here we see it takes
内存，但是如果我们去这里，我们会发现
now the JVM already fix out is 130
现在JVM已经解决了130
megabyte of RAM but it has too much RAM
兆字节的RAM，但它有太多的RAM
assigned so there is no pressure on the
分配，因此没有压力
on the garbage collector to collect that
在垃圾收集器上收集
unfortunately I will have to kill
不幸的是我将不得不杀死
everything Java related this happens
与Java相关的所有事情
with profiling because of class sharing
通过类共享进行分析
and just we do this so and then I will
然后我们这样做，然后我会
just show you and I would then implement
只是告诉你，我会实施
a small war deployed and measure the
展开一场小规模的战争并衡量
performance and see where the overhead
性能并查看开销
actually is and then start these swarms
其实是然后开始这些群
so after the payara swarm and the hollow
所以在薪ara群和空心
swarm how it feels like and was the
蜂拥而至
difference then you can then use it with
差异，那么您可以将其与
CD numbers good strategy if not we can
CD号如果不是可以的话，很好的策略
do something else but I try to know to
做其他事情，但我尝试知道
see what it how much whatever you can
看看有多少你能
actually save yes
实际保存是
yeah always actually
是的，实际上
so we perform stress tests all the time
所以我们一直在进行压力测试
and I will actually create an
我实际上将创建一个
application if you like a GB with
如果您喜欢GB，则使用该应用程序
transactions and see the its the most
交易，看到它是最
of that and then if you have that all
然后，如果您拥有全部
aspects are loaded to be no much
方面加载不多
difference but you're right if the
区别，但是如果
Immigration Service a super smart they
移民局他们超级聪明
would start nothing right and then if it
不会正确开始，然后如果开始
deployed first one but you will see
部署第一个，但您会看到
there will no difference actually so um
其实没有什么区别
so actually very good point so most of
所以实际上很好，所以大多数
my clients they they run with two
我的客户他们与两个
gigabyte of RAM in my perspective I
我认为GB的RAM
would assign more because there is you
会分配更多的，因为有你
know what's the point what they just
知道他们的意思是什么
like it so this is the most whitefly
喜欢，所以这是最粉虱
payara they run with - exam mix to geek
他们一起运行的payara-极客考试组合
and of course this say nothing because
当然，这什么也没说，因为
if you start to cash in your application
如果您开始兑现您的申请
you know it really depends what we are
你知道这真的取决于我们
doing so monitor now we have the payara
这样做监视现在我们有薪金
wheter from the garbage collection and
从垃圾收集和
you see is again 41 max so it seems like
你再看是41最大，所以看起来
the 40 megabyte is is the absolute limit
40兆字节是绝对限制
no limit
没有限制
all these servers are 40 Mac and the
所有这些服务器都是40 Mac，
Tomcat I test it once around 10 Meg so
Tomcat我大约在10 Meg左右测试过一次
this is what you can Tomcat or jetty but
这就是你可以Tomcat或码头，但
though it is 6 megabyte more they can
虽然可以再增加6兆字节
say Tomcat is bloated because as twice
说Tomcat肿是因为两次
as big as my service orchid right so but
和我的兰花一样大，但是
you know the arguments is if you know
你知道论据是，如果你知道
the numbers I mean what's the problem
数字我的意思是什么问题
okay that's a one full time I mean
好吧，那是我的全职
heavyweight is meaningless
重量级的人没有意义
agreed so now we have payara and so
同意，所以现在我们有payara等
let's implement a something so and
让我们实现一些事情
yesterday i was on the how it's called
昨天我在如何称呼它
keynote Oracle code keynote and there
主题演讲Oracle代码主题演讲
were lots of FAS FAS right you know what
有很多FAS FAS对，你知道吗
it is
它是
food as a service right so this is what
食物即服务，所以这就是
should be scalable here so um I would
应该在这里可扩展，所以我会
like to create a project what I did
喜欢创建一个我所做的项目
yesterday and just taught it back
昨天刚教回来
migrated back to Java EE 7 because I
迁移回Java EE 7，因为我
would like to use all the service and
想要使用所有服务，
this 8 would only run on GlassFish 5 and
这个8只能在GlassFish 5上运行，
it comes with one it comes with nothing
它带有一个，它一无所有
in the built
在建
so then I would create a Java class and
因此，我将创建一个Java类，
call it food serve food resource with an
称其为食物服务食物资源
end point and the end point is food and
终点，终点是食物和
one cat and I would just go with that -
一只猫，我会只用它-
usually I would just that we have an EJB
通常我只会拥有EJB
already and then string get and then
已经然后字符串get然后
because you asked me this I would like
因为你问我我想
to get and also activate dependency
获得并激活依赖性
injection so I would say food manager
注射，所以我要说食物经理
all enterprise apps need a manager
所有企业应用程序都需要一位经理
then another stateless beam and this
然后是另一个无状态光束
stateless beam has a or we can do
无状态光束有一个或我们可以做的
request cope or whatever like but
要求应付或类似
stateless I think many say eg bees are
无状态我想很多人都说蜜蜂
the heaviest so was the request scope
最重的是请求范围
they would be slower so I'm happy to do
他们会慢一些，所以我很高兴做
it with stateless so but food and what
它是无状态的，但是食物又是什么
we get is already got the yesterday
我们已经得到了昨天
salad of course salad so decorated
沙拉当然是这样装饰的沙拉
sanitary incorporated salad and some
卫生沙拉和一些
random noise so we have this save it and
随机噪声，因此我们将其保存下来，
then I can inject the food manager FM
那我可以给食品经理调频
and here's a return this.f m dot food I
这是this.fm点食品的回报，我
think it's enough so I'm just the
认为足够了，所以我只是
adjacent object I will leave it so it
相邻的对象我会离开它
will be as fast so this JSON object
会快到这个JSON对象
doesn't make a lot difference and I hope
没什么大不了，我希望
wait a second
等一会儿
that all the payara is running so let's
所有的薪水都在运行，所以让我们
deploy it and payara so run and I would
部署它，并运行payara，我会
lose payara right now
现在失去payara
so as to say there is not a lot
可以说没有很多
difference between the application
应用之间的差异
service regarding the overhead or
有关开销的服务或
runtime performance I mean they
我的意思是运行时性能
optimising like crazy over the years so
多年来疯狂地优化，所以
resources food so resources food and cat
资源食物所以资源食物和猫
was it wrong
错了吗
miss Perry something
佩里小姐的东西
functions are service okay resources and
功能是可以服务的资源，
food yeah works so now we have here an
食物不错，所以现在我们在这里
app to EG bees with an injection I mean
我的意思是注射到EG蜜蜂上
in real world we will get probably
在现实世界中，我们可能会
another AG bees with some injection so
另一只AG蜜蜂注射了些东西
we could measure the difference and I
我们可以衡量差异，而我
would like to use JPA because most of
想要使用JPA，因为大多数
the spring drop Wizard project have also
Spring Drop Wizard项目也有
GPA so there is nothing to compare so
GPA所以没有什么可比的
what I would like to compare the
我想比较的是
applications of a specific stuff like
特定事物的应用，例如
CDI and eg bees this is what we can
CDI和蜜蜂，这就是我们所能做的
where the overhead might come from right
开销可能来自正确的地方
so we have the GlassFish that will
所以我们有GlassFish
connect to that and then what I would
连接到那，然后我会
like to do is a nice tool called Apache
喜欢做的是一个很好的工具，叫做Apache
benchmarks it comes with Apache and is
Apache随附的基准测试
available on all platforms if you
如果您在所有平台上都可以使用
install Apache web server we have the
安装Apache Web服务器
tool - see is this number of concurrent
工具-请参阅此并发数量
processes let's say 5 - n is the number
流程说5-n是数字
of requests and I can say 1000 and go
的请求，我可以说1000再走
with that
接着就，随即
what's problem yeah - and thank you so
是什么问题，是的-谢谢你
as you can see right now is requests per
如您现在所见，每个请求
second is 1,400 which is surprisingly
第二个是1,400，这令人惊讶
low and we can look now and the monitor
低，我们现在可以看一下显示器
and we see perform GC and doesn't have
而且我们看到执行GC并没有
really doesn't affect a lot I mean
真的没有多大影响
there's a little bit right because it's
有一点是对的，因为
loaded and everything is initiated but
加载并启动所有内容，但
if I do it again and perform GC it goes
如果我再做一次并执行GC，它将成功
back to about 60 and this is the usual
回到大约60，这是通常的
behavior and all app so there's actually
行为和所有应用程序，因此实际上
I would argue if the application gets
我会争辩说，如果申请得到
larger and you have some day then you
更大，你有一天，那么你
get entitymanager with caches and
获取带有缓存的entitymanager，并
concurrent transactions that there are
有并发事务
lots of RAM but this was never a problem
大量的RAM，但这从来不是问题
so I mean jelly from the beginning and I
所以我的意思是从一开始就是果冻
never saw a project where we have to
从来没有见过我们必须做的项目
migrate away from application server
从应用服务器迁移
because it was too big too slow or
因为它太大，太慢或
whatever and always a fault transaction
无论什么，总是错误的交易
from transactions handling locking or
来自处理锁定的交易或
whatever I am so we did this
无论我是什么，我们都这样做了
now there's another tool a little bit
现在有另一种工具
more convenient and work deft procs
更方便，更轻松的工作
tools and this is called J Mita three
工具，这叫做J Mita三
one and this one yeah it starts so I can
一个，这个开始，所以我可以
say I would like to have a thread group
说我想有一个线程组
with five threads and it should run
有五个线程，它应该运行
forever and ramp-up is okay and then
永远，然后加速就可以了，然后
what I do I add a sampler HTTP request
我要添加一个采样器HTTP请求
and this is the path so it and the I
这就是道路，而我
need the localhost here and 8080 so fast
需要 localhost 和8080这么快
resources food and then one thing is
资源食物，然后一件事是
called listener and I only would like to
叫听众，我只想
have the thing is called
有东西叫
summary report yes this is what I'm
摘要报告是的，这就是我
usually need and I say start know and it
通常需要，我说开始就知道了
is important that here is zero errors it
重要的是这里的零错误
means this is the actual stress test so
表示这是实际的压力测试，因此
and this once this is what we do at the
这就是我们在
beginning of the projects to see you
开始见你的项目
know how much resources do we need so
知道我们需要多少资源
this is the my usual operations lag and
这是我通常的操作滞后，
doing this on conferences just to get
在会议上这样做只是为了
you know an idea what the application
你知道一个想法是什么应用
service doing so and then you see here
服务这样做，然后您会在这里看到
CPU usage is 60 so it is not a very good
CPU使用率是60，所以不是很好
stress test because it should be 80 so
压力测试，因为应该是80
it is and we see here the TDD in needs
是的，我们在这里看到需要的TDD
more memory but if I perform the garbage
更多的内存，但是如果我执行垃圾
collection it always goes back to our
收集总是可以追溯到我们的
around 60 and the heavy load and now
大约60和沉重的负担，现在
comes the cool thing what I would like
来了我想要的很酷的东西
to measure is the true overhead of the
要衡量的是
ejbs interceptors and dependency
ejbs拦截器和依赖项
injection so I would like to switch to
注射，所以我想切换到
to simpler and see CPU sampling so now
更简单并查看CPU采样，所以现在
this is like profiling with very very
这就像非常非常
low overhead and what I see here is that
低开销，我在这里看到的是
the most overhead is sync threat verka
开销最大的是同步威胁Verka
get tasks and I think the reason is I
得到任务，我认为原因是我
miss configured the payara was to have
小姐配置了薪水是
just five threats doesn't really matter
只是五个威胁并不重要
but the cool story is there are no no
但很酷的故事是没有
each Ibiza so the first page it seems
每个伊维萨岛，所以首页似乎
likes to eg bees and all the stuff do
喜欢蜜蜂，所有的东西都喜欢
not consume any cpu cycles in relation
不消耗任何CPU周期
to the other stuff
到其他东西
and what you should do and just
和你应该做什么，只是
searching for my package and this is you
搜索我的包裹，这就是你
see these two classes they this are the
看到这两个类，这是
overhead of eg B's these are the
例如B的开销是
interceptors or the proxies which start
拦截器或开始的代理
transactions measure monitoring
交易指标监控
performance as you can see is the
如您所见，性能是
overhead of egb in total is zero one
egb的总开销为零1
percent so if it would remove eg B's we
百分比，因此，如果它可以删除例如B
could say that most 900 milliseconds
可以说最多900毫秒
during a test so it is pointless so
在测试过程中，这是没有意义的
actually I never had a stress test where
其实我从来没有做过压力测试
the eg B's appeared on the top if we
例如，如果我们将B出现在顶部
have HTTP layer and this is natural of
有HTTP层，这很自然
course because the HTTP layer does a lot
当然是因为HTTP层做了很多
of work they have parsed the HTTP
他们已经解析了HTTP的工作
protocol start the threads we our should
协议启动我们应该使用的线程
be but for unknown reasons most of the
但由于未知原因，大多数
task force tried to go away from CDI and
工作队试图摆脱CDI和
eg B's they implemented their own
例如B他们实行了自己的
framework which never worked and then we
框架从未奏效，然后我们
roll back to stand out and it work again
退后脱颖而出，它又能正常工作
what became boring again and properly
什么又变得无聊了
you can call it now heavyweight ok so my
你现在可以称它为重量级，所以我
point is here in architectures you know
关键是你知道的架构
you should measure first and premature
你应该先测量并过早
optimization is the root of all evil in
优化是万恶之源
architecture because if you will create
体系结构，因为如果您要创建
your own slow snowflakes with undertow
拖着你自己的慢雪花
in jax-rs
在jax-rs中
no one will get why you did this and
没有人会明白你为什么这样做，
there will be no support any questions
不会有任何问题的支持
about this so then I would like so my
关于这个，那么我想这样我的
CPU is hot right now so but I would like
CPU现在很热，所以我想
to switch let's see
切换让我们看看
who is from payara your Pyro's just have
谁是来自payara的您的Pyro所拥有的
priority I forgot always do you
优先拉屎我忘了总是你
read domain monitoring I think now
我现在想阅读域监视
monitoring domain yes
监视域是
server transaction service as you can
可以的服务器交易服务
see we started in our tests 177,000 on 1
看到我们从17,000的测试开始
million transactions and there are no
百万笔交易，没有
rollbacks so what we got also now a
回滚，所以我们现在还得到了
complete complete complete monitoring
完成完全完全监视
with a full stack out of the box and
开箱即用
this is true for white fly if your
如果您的白蝇是真的，
Liberty profile all application servers
Liberty配置所有应用程序服务器
this is what you get for free if you
这是您免费获得的东西
start with your own undertow and jax-rs
从您自己的秘密和jax-rs开始
we have nothing if you have jealousy or
如果您有嫉妒，我们什么也没有
a little bit but you get it for free and
一点点，但您可以免费获得
the cool story is I can have it up Jason
最酷的故事是我可以拿下杰森
so I can create a decent you know react
所以我可以创造一个体面的你知道的反应
app to monitor that or if you have a
应用程序来监视它，或者如果您有
service bus of course you can consume
您当然可以使用服务巴士
XML if you like years B's ok so this is
XML，如果您喜欢B的年份，那么这是
what you get for free and all the
您免费获得的一切
bulkheads and are also included no time
舱壁，也没有时间
to mention this yeah yeah this is what I
提这个，是的，这就是我
said this this last test is the highest
说这最后的测试是最高的
possible overhead because what I did
可能的开销，因为我做了什么
here they're here in payara and my
在这里，他们在payara，而我
service always run in full monitor
服务始终在完整监视器中运行
configure you can see this is my
配置你可以看到这是我的
standard setup all monitoring even color
标准设置，所有监控甚至彩色
bar which is not used is high so the
没有使用的酒吧很高，所以
highest possible sampling and monitoring
尽可能高的采样和监控
level so and this is why because we
如此水平，这就是为什么，因为我们
measure in all the stress test in all
在所有压力测试中进行全面测量
our our tests was the highest possible
我们的测试是最高的
monitoring if is good enough we can go
监视是否足够好我们可以去
in production with the highest possible
在生产中以最高的可能
monitoring and if not I will deactivated
监控，如果没有，我将停用
so we always do as high as possible
所以我们总是做得尽可能高
monitoring Wi-Fi the same so the first
监控Wi-Fi同样如此
thing I do I activate everything so the
我做的事会激活所有东西，所以
activating is not that easy but what you
激活不是那么容易，但是你
will never do you will never activate
永远不会做，你永远不会激活
something in production right but if
生产中有东西，但是如果
everything is tested stress tested there
一切都经过测试压力测试在那里
is not a problem
不是问题
so this was the worst possible
所以这是最糟糕的可能
performance you can achieve and this was
您可以实现的性能，这是
the slowest possible thing usually have
通常最慢的东西
around 5,000 to 10,000 transactions per
每笔交易约5,000至10,000笔交易
second as a
第二作为
transactions per second in this setup
此设置中的每秒事务数
and this is the overhead included of eg
这是例如
B's of course there is no business logic
B当然没有业务逻辑
but I mean if you introduce business
但我的意思是如果您介绍业务
logic do be pointless the whole
逻辑确实毫无意义
conversation I agreed questions No
对话我同意了问题否
then I would like to stop payara and
然后我想停止payara和
then go to junk again and junk because I
然后再次去垃圾，因为我
would delete it afterwards Java - Jarrah
以后将其删除Java-Jarrah
payara micro now it's the micro and I
payara micro现在是micro，我
can say deploy please I think it's this
可以说部署，我想就是这个
way deploy FAS should be target and then
部署FAS的方式应该是目标，然后
we have here FIS
我们这里有FIS
so now the PI are micro started and this
所以现在PI是微启动的
is what I really like in micro payara
我真的很喜欢微支付
you download this it can do this so what
您下载它可以做到这一点
is the in my eyes the ultimate use case
在我眼中是最终用例
for micro it is simpler if you just need
对于微型，如果您只需要，它会更简单
this so if you have to create an docker
因此，如果您必须创建一个泊坞窗
file you have just one thing you don't
文件，你只有一件事，而你没有
have to unzip so the docket files a
必须解压缩，以便档案文件
little bit simpler but hence I have all
有点简单，但是因此我拥有了所有
the documents it's not a big issue for
对于文件来说这不是一个大问题
me but if you are starting with Java I
我，但是如果您从Java开始，
mean this is nice to see something like
表示看到这样的东西真是太好了
this
这个
so um paella micro monitor 170 used so
所以嗯西班牙海鲜饭微型监视器170
so performed GC it goes back to about
因此执行GC可以回溯到大约
there are 30 and back to 5060 I would
有30然后回到5060
say the same almost you had to make to
说差不多你必须做的
the a reproducible test I will have to
可重复的测试，我将不得不
kill all the JVM switched on my laptop
杀死笔记本电脑上所有打开的JVM
but you see it is in the same ballpark
但你看到它在同一个球场
right agreed so um and the jmeter I
没错，所以嗯，我
could start no oh we had seen 10,000
可以开始不了哦，我们已经看到了10,000
transactions per second you saw this
您看到的每秒交易数
there were 10,000 so now we have 4000
有10,000，所以现在有4000
this is PI R now micro but there were
这是现在的PI R micro，但是有
10,000 so it wound up so I forgot to
10,000所以清盘所以我忘了
show you now it's called cuts high in
现在向您展示它被称为高切
higher okay and whitefly Hollow so now
更高，还可以，粉虱为空心，所以现在
it's we had a swarm and we have D hollow
这是我们有一群，我们有D空心
swarm
一群
now this is actually the thing to use
现在这实际上是要使用的东西
the hollow swarm it means it is ready to
空心的蜂群意味着它已经准备好
use profile and you only have to specify
使用配置文件，您只需指定
the app so you don't have you notice
该应用程序，因此您不会注意到
that the whole mavin hell with all the
整个马文地狱与所有
dependency issues I don't get it you
依赖性问题我不明白你
don't have to do this so and this is
不必这样做，这是
absolute nice so what I can say is Java
绝对不错，所以我可以说是Java
- char micro profile swarm and then
-字符微轮廓群，然后
point just to the same to the two DFAS
指向两个DFAS相同
and it starts you see it started the
它开始，您看到它开始了
JAXA res CD I'm Jason bean very dense
JAXA res CD我是Jason bean，非常密集
transactions undertow and jax-rs and
交易和jax-rs以及
then it said this is the advice that is
然后说这是建议
ready so um what is the overhead monitor
准备好了，什么是开销监视器
this was where is it Apache don't see it
这是Apache在哪里，看不到它
like oh yeah is it monitor 70 used
就像哦，是吗，它是显示器70
perform GC goes back to 30 so it's the
执行GC会回到30，这是
first micro which you could save 10 max
第一个微型，最多可以节省10个
someone asked me the question you know
有人问我你知道的问题
what is my opinion by micro you seen out
你看到我对我的看法是什么
the numbers now is your choice if you
如果您现在选择数字
would like to save 10 Meg use micro okay
想省下10兆，用微型好吗
and the problem with a little bit of is
和一点点的问题是
marketing so payara is great but if you
营销，所以payara很棒，但是如果您
go to white fly swarm this is what I get
去白蝇成群，这就是我得到的
a lot of questions so first right size
很多问题，所以先选择合适的尺寸
your services it implies something is
您的服务暗示着
too big right and then if you try this
太大，然后再尝试
you see this simple project setup I mean
您会看到这个简单的项目设置
it's too hard for a session from scratch
从头开始的会话太难了
right so and the cool story is what you
是的，很酷的故事就是你
get then you will have to rebuild the
得到那么你将不得不重建
Piatt ad sorry there there the the white
皮亚特广告对不起那里的白色
fly and you app over and over again okay
飞，你的应用程序一遍又一遍好
now the last thing build times and
现在，最后一件事是建造时间，
docker and clouds very important thing
码头工人和云非常重要的事情
someone said what about clouds why the
有人说云怎么办
micro is smaller so that now I would
微小，所以我现在
like to show you this okay so kill the
想给你看这个好吧，所以杀死
swarm and then go to FAS and now I have
蜂拥而至，去FAS，现在我有了
my maven project so what I can do
我的Maven项目，所以我能做什么
do a little bit larger I can say maven
做大一点我可以说行家
clean package
清洁包装
and it builds the app right so what I
它可以正确构建应用程序
can do right now I can say maven package
现在可以做我可以说Maven包
and and nothing because I forgot a
而且什么也没有，因为我忘记了
docker file so we need in FAS and I will
docker文件，所以我们需要FAS，我将
say I need here other and the docker
说我需要其他和码头工人
file and what I have to say is is from
文件，我要说的是来自
this is my own doctor repository X let's
这是我自己的医生资料库X让我们
say white lie wild wild sly I forgot to
说白谎我忘了
show you Tommy Tommy is very similar to
显示汤米汤米汤米与
Liberty very very small that Tommy and I
自由很小，我和汤米
always used it Tommy plus so Tommy is
总是用汤米加，所以汤米是
also great copy target FAS dot war into
也将目标FAS点战争复制到
deployment there so this is the
在那里部署，所以这是
dockerfile and now I can say Doka build
dockerfile，现在我可以说多卡构建了
- tea Java one FAA food as a service dot
-茶JAVA一种FAA食品即服务点
ministy built so now you have fully
建造的小巧，所以你现在已经完全
executable image you can push to the
您可以将可执行映像推送到
cloud so we can do it again now try the
云计算，因此我们现在可以再次尝试
same with fetch ours so in last project
与获取我们的一样，所以在上一个项目中
they use a technology would not to
他们使用技术不会
mention so simple boot took 40 seconds
提起这么简单的启动花了40秒钟
all the dependencies were pulled and the
所有的依赖都被拉了
service was right the service was right
服务是对的服务是对的
sighs afterwards but why I have to say
之后叹了口气，但为什么我要说
to wait 40 seconds just to see to build
等待40秒只是为了看建造
open over game the same stuff
在游戏中打开相同的东西
therefore the killer tip here use the
因此，这里的杀手tip
hollow swarm or micro profile don't even
空心群或微轮廓甚至都没有
try to build a server over and over
尝试一遍又一遍地构建服务器
again doesn't make any sense
再次没有任何意义
now a little bit of cheating because
现在有点作弊，因为
docker images and what you see here is
泊坞窗图片，您在这里看到的是
the following
下列
there's a lot of images wait a second so
有很多图像等一下
this this is the last image so food as a
这是最后一张图片，所以食物
service and this is a 560 Meg of RAM of
服务，这是560 Meg的RAM
disk by disk space as you can see if I
您可以按磁盘空间逐个查看磁盘
build it again this is 560 over and over
再次建立它是560反复
again so if you see just Alliance I
再一次，如果你看到的只是联盟我
think no way that man hard discuss then
认为那个男人不敢再讨论
not space so something wrong with the
没有空间，所以出问题了
display right and now I show you
显示正确，现在我告诉你
something doctor history j1 FAS now is
医生历史j1 FAS现在是
the killer feature of application
应用程序的杀手feature
servers using the application service in
使用应用程序服务的服务器
the clouds and thin Wars if you do this
乌云密布的战争，如果你这样做
look at that there's ah yeah okay so
看看那里是啊，是的，所以
what you see here the first layer is the
您在这里看到的第一层是
centers operating system was built six
中心建六操作系统
months ago
几个月前
now here I built this is Java six month
现在在这里我建了这是Java六个月
ago Java eight 200 mix then four months
以前Java八百种混合，然后四个月
ago I created a white flag and these are
以前我创建了一个白旗，这些是
the layers and the cool story is what we
层和很酷的故事是我们
built to Dell today about one minute ago
今天大约在一分钟前为戴尔制造
is 4k
是4k
so and this is why you always need the
所以这就是为什么你总是需要
separation between the infrastructure
基础设施之间的分离
and the war and the cool story is what
战争和很酷的故事是什么
you do in the clouds you get too much in
你在云端做得太多
em add some vegetables for example it's
EM添加一些蔬菜，例如
German you get in Amazon Google Cloud
您在Amazon Google Cloud中获得的德语
Asia or jelastic your private docker
亚洲还是让您的私人码头工人变得僵化
registry and you will push the 560
注册表，您将推动560
megabytes minus the 3k once ok and then
兆字节减去3k，然后确定
what they are pushing the docker is like
他们推动码头工人的方式就像
a kid has been understands that nothing
一个孩子一直不知道
change or delays are the same then you
变化或延迟是相同的，那么你
would only push the three case therefore
因此只会推这三种情况
in all my cloud projects were crazy fast
我所有的云项目都快疯了
because pushing to the cloud it took no
因为推到云端不需要
transfer of three kilobyte but if I
传输三千字节，但如果我
would use let's say the swarm without
会说，没有
the holo I will create first my build
我将首先创建我的构建
would be crazy slow I would have to
会很疯狂，我不得不
build in maven all the things and my jar
将所有东西和罐子放在Maven中
would be let's wait a second city junk
让我们等第二个城市垃圾
LS Minos so you see the nanos this is
LS Minos，所以您看到的是nanos
hollow swarm is 86 Mac and micro are 60
空心群是86 Mac，微型群是60
Meg so what it means I will push each
梅格，这意味着我要推动每个
time 62 max plus 3 kilobyte to the to
时间最大为62，再加上3 KB
the cloud and this is significant okay
云，这很重要
so this is when you have Clyde clouds
所以这是当你有克莱德云
you have to really have a good reasons
你必须有一个很好的理由
to use fetch our super jars I don't even
用拿来我们甚至没有的超级罐子
get it I asked many times and the most
得到它，我问过很多次了
reasonable answer I got why they use
合理的答案我知道为什么他们使用
uber jars in one project say they
在一个项目中的超级罐子说
started before docker and back then they
在docker之前开始，然后他们
didn't you better so this would I
你不是更好，所以我会
understand but right now it does make
了解，但现在确实可以
any sense if you think from software
如果你从软件上考虑
engineering perspective why I should be
工程学角度我为什么要
built over and over again the same stuff
一遍又一遍地建立相同的东西
with only three kilobyte out of 60
在60中只有3 KB
changes if I will migrate everything to
如果我将所有内容都迁移到
the pump I will I will build the 60 max
泵，我将制造60最大
over and over again why if you know the
一遍又一遍为什么你知道
answer you can give me now or we can
回答你可以现在给我，或者我们可以
move out and but I have no idea okay so
搬出去，但我不知道好吗
I think we're almost done with the time
我想时间已经差不多了
right any questions because I have night
回答任何问题，因为我晚上
next session right
下届会议权
yeah very simple if the client has
是的，如果客户有
already you know contract with red head
你已经知道与红头合同
white life if they have Tomcat Tommy and
如果他们有Tomcat Tommy和
and if they have something with glasses
如果他们戴着眼镜，
or Sun payara and I don't care I use in
或Sun payara，我不在乎我用在
my projects Tommy pyar and white fight
我的项目Tommy pyar和白人斗争
never micro so far I like micro but I
到目前为止，我从未喜欢过微型，但我
wouldn't why because if you have to
不会为什么，因为如果您必须
configure them there's you need the same
配置他们那里你需要相同的
XML file somewhere there's not like you
不像您这样的地方的XML文件
need never need a configuration yeah
永远不需要配置是的
this is what I really completely against
这是我真正完全反对的
so in my project you will have two
所以在我的项目中，您将有两个
really good reasons to do this so I
这样做的确有很好的理由，所以我
don't get it still and I never got an
不要把它拿走，我永远也不会
answer why to do this because in the
回答为什么要这样做，因为在
rules docker and clouds is absolutely
规则码头工人和云绝对
irrelevant and also I got in Docklands
无关紧要，我也到了港区
pull requests you know to use alpine
拉取您知道使用高山的要求
Linux instead of sent OS but Luke sent
Linux，而不是已发送的操作系统，但Luke已发送
to us the commands all my clients know
给我所有客户都知道的命令
with Alpine I would say if 100 makes per
我会说如果每100个
machine once the machine who cares about
机器曾经在乎的机器
that you know this is the same story so
你知道这是同一个故事，所以
we can argue then make a linear or what
我们可以争论然后做出线性或什么
Lina who who cares about one other
互相关心的丽娜
megabyte of this space right and yeah
是这个空间的兆字节，是的
this is what I can tell you in five
这就是我可以在五个中告诉你的
years before you could complete
数年才能完成
different answer I would say you use
我会说你用不同的答案
GlassFish but the reason was grass which
GlassFish但原因是草
was the reference implementation for
是的参考实现
which you could buy support and this was
您可以购买支持，这是
unique right something like this was
像这样的独特权利是
never before but right now there is no
从来没有，但是现在没有
support for GlassFish but there is
支持GlassFish，但有
support for payara
支持payara
it's also nice because if you get PI R 5
这也很好，因为如果您获得PI R 5
it makes appealing because last fish V 5
之所以吸引人，是因为最后一条鱼V 5
is the reference implementation for Java
是Java的参考实现
8 and payara 5 I guess will be the
8和payara 5我猜会是
etched glass which where you can buy
蚀刻玻璃在哪里可以买到
support so they have a slight advantage
支持，所以他们有一点优势
I would say ok then thank you I have to
我会说好，然后谢谢你，我必须
go to the next session if you need ugly
如果您需要丑陋，请参加下一个课程
sticker
贴图
you
您